freecultr.com 2015-11-09

# Privacy Policy | Lifestyle Apparel Brand | FREECULTR

[Freecultr.com](http://www.freecultr.com/) knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.   **By visiting the Website & using our platform, you are accepting this Privacy Policy.**

  1. **Collection of Information**
    1. **Purpose**. The information we learn from customers allows us to personalize and continually improve the total shopping experience at the Website.
    2. **Cookies**. When you visit our site, unique cookies are placed on your browser. We assign a cookie to your computer when you first visit us in order to enable us to recognize you each time you return. Through cookies we can customize our Website to your individual preferences in order to create a more personalized, convenient shopping experience. Please note that the cookies we use for our Website or email campaigns do not store personally identifiable information about you or your finances.    

  2. **Sharing of Information**
    1. **General**. The information that we collect about our customers is critical to our business. We respect and value this information, and do not want to jeopardize the flow of information between our customers and the Website. Therefore, we are not in the business of selling this information to other websites or businesses. There are very limited circumstances where we do share some customer information with our subsidiaries that either are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Policy. 

  3. **Information Security**
    1. **SSL Certification**. All information provided by You to the Website is protected under SSL Certification
    2. **Data Safety** \- The Website uses Amazon Secure Server for all Order Confirmations.
    3. **Signing off**. To prevent unauthorized access to sensitive information, it is important for you to monitor those who have access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. Please note that the Website does not store any Credit Card information and redirects all payment requests to third party payment gateways.       
  4. **User Access to Information**
    1. **General**. When you access your account, there is a variety of information that you will see. This is designed to allow you to update any changed information and view the information that you entered previously. This information is sensitive, and it is necessary to both protect this information and keep it current in order to have the best experience on the Website.

  5. **User Choices with regard to Access of Information**
    1. **General**. You always have the right to refrain from providing any information. This may have an impact on use of the Website and on the ease of making purchases or taking advantage of certain unique features of the Website.
    2. **Prior Information.** You can add or update certain information on pages such as those listed in the “User Access to Information” section above. 
    3. **Customer Communication.** If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your account setting regarding email contact preferences. (You cannot waive the applicability of the Conditions of Use and other legal notices, such as this Privacy Policy, and if you elect not receive those notices, they will still govern your use of the Website, and it is your responsibility to review them for changes.
    4. **Cookie Choices.** The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, affecting the acceptance of cookies means that you will not be able to use such important features as accelerated ordering and customized product suggestions.
    5. **Anonymous Browsing.** A large number of products may be accessed without the use of cookies or anonymously. 

  6. **Children**
    1. **General**. If you are under age 18, you may use the Website only with the consent of a parent or guardian.

  7. **Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**
    1. **Acceptance of conditions of use.** By visiting the Website, you accept that your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to various terms and conditions of the Website as incorporated in, inter alia, this Privacy Policy, the User Agreement, the IP Policy etc. including but not limited to limitations on damage, arbitration of disputes etc.If you have any concern about privacy at the Website, please send us a thorough description to[*], and we will try to resolve it.
    2. **Revisions**. Because our business changes constantly, we reserve the right to periodically revise the terms and conditions for use of the Website including the present Privacy Policy. Prior to making these changes, we will e-mail periodic reminder of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
    3. **Applicability**. Unless stated otherwise, the present Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

  8. **Information You Gave Us**
    1. **General**. Information is collected from you when you do the following activities: search, buy, create an account, post a review or opinion, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service.
    2. **Examples**. For example, information would be collected when a user came to the Website, searched for a product, placed an order through the Website, created a store, signed up, updated your information in your account settings, added items to your wish list, called or e-mailed customer service, reviewed a product, participated in a discussion or chat, completed a questionnaire or a contest entry form;.
    3. **Information that could be supplied.** As a result of any of the above actions, it is possible that you will supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; bank account details, credit/debit card information; purchase and shipping recipients, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers) listed in rapid order processing settings; content of reviews and e-mails to us; personal description and photograph in personal section; and financial information.

  9. **Automatic Information**
    1. **General**. As Discussed earlier, our systems collect information that is sent over the internet without your control.
    2. **Examples**. Some examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as bestsellers and product suggestions; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Website, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; closeout shops you visited; your auction history; and the phone number you used to call our toll-free number.
    3. **Software Used.** During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs0, and methods used to browse away from the page.

  10. **Information from Other Sources**
    1. **General**. Occasionally, we supplement the information that we receive that has been outlined above with information from other sources and companies. Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or redemption information; search term and search result information; credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers.

  11. **Changes to this Privacy Policy**
    1. We may update this policy and we will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on the Website.
